Daniel Lewis Jones

E-Mail: danieljones314@gmail.com Date of Birth: 3rd May 1989

Cell: 1 604 358 4347

I have valuable sales experience working as an outbound telesales agent for an insurance company and as a lead generator in door-to-door sales. I am a highly self-motivated individual with a proven track record of success both academically and in the workplace.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-2018: Internal Telesales Agent for Freedom Insurance Group

Within 6 months I became one of the top selling agents at the company, always achieving and surpassing my weekly targets. Assisted with training new staff and running daily team meetings.

2016 - 2017: Lead Generator for NewGen Energy

Worked as a door to door lead generator, selling solar panels in rural NSW. I regularly achieved strong results for the company.

2012 - 2016: High School Geography Teacher

Teacher of Geography, involving managing classes of up to 35 children. Strong organisational and time management skills required. I have developed my ability to communicate effectively with people both verbally and in written form.

2009 - 2011: Planning Consultant at Asbri Planning

Worked full time as a planning consultant for 18 months. This role involved managing development teams and consulting with other professionals.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2013 Course	Swansea Metropolitan University – High School Teacher Training
2007 - 2011	Cardiff University - BSc City and Regional Planning 2:1 Honours
2000 - 2007	Strade High School 3 A Levels (equivalent of High School Certificate): Business (B), Physical Education (B), Geography (C).

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Web design: I run a website design business in my own time.
- Learning French as third language.
- Team Sports.
- Travelling.

SKILLS

- Strong organizational and leadership skills. These were essential during previous employment as a Planner and Teacher.
- I.T. literate in a range of packages including Word, Excel, Adobe Photoshop, WordPress.
- Full driving license.